Crusade for Opportunity Records
Crusade for Opportunity Records
- Administrative files
  - Job descriptions
    - Coding Supervisor, undated (Box 42)
    - Community Development Aide and Worker, undated (Box 42)
    - Community Services Specialist, undated (Box 42)
    - Community Services Specialist, 1966 (Box 42)
    - Counselor, undated (Box 42)
    - Crew Chief, undated (Box 42)
    - Deputy Director for Administration, 1966 (Box 42)
    - Deputy Director for Community Services, undated (Box 42)
    - Deputy Director for Training, undated (Box 42)
    - Editorial Assistant, 1966 (Box 42)
    - Education Materials Development Specialist, undated (Box 42)
    - Education Specialist, undated (Box 42)
    - Educational Specialist, 1966 (Box 42)
    - Field Operations Director, undated (Box 42)
    - Financial Director, undated (Box 42)
    - In-School Counselor, undated (Box 42)
    - In-School Secretary, undated (Box 42)
    - In-Service Training Officer, undated (Box 42)
    - In-Service Training Director, undated; 2 folders (Box 42)
    - Insurance Clerk, undated (Box 42)
    - Intake Clerk, undated (Box 42)
    - Intake Worker, undated (Box 42)
    - Intake Statistics and Office Supervisor, undated (Box 42)
    - Intake Secretary, undated (Box 42)
    - Intern (Professional Aide), undated (Box 42)
    - Inventory Clerk (GSA), undated (Box 42)
    - Job Classifications, undated (Box 42)
    - Job Classifications, 1966-1967 (Box 42)
    - Job Corps Coordinator, undated (Box 42)
    - Job description drafts, 1964 (Box 42)
    - Job Development Specialist, undated (Box 43)
    - Legal Services, undated (Box 43)
    - Mail Clerk, undated (Box 43)
    - Mail-Stock Clerk, undated (Box 43)
    - Neighborhood Youth Corps, Guidance Counselors, 1965 (Box 43)
    - NYC In-School Counselor, undated (Box 43)
    - Office Manager, undated (Box 43)
    - Original copies to be used only for making copies to put into the job description files (Box 43)
    - Part-Time Teacher, undated (Box 43)
    - Payroll Clerk, undated; 2 folders (Box 43)
    - Payroll Supervisor, undated; 2 folders (Box 43)
    - Personnel Director, undated (Box 43)
    - Personnel Officer, undated (Box 43)
    - Program Development Director, 1965 (Box 43)
    - Project Engineer, undated (Box 43)
    - Program Coordinator, undated (Box 43)
    - Program Development Specialist, undated (Box 43)
    - Public Affairs Assistant, undated (Box 43)
    - Public Affairs Writer, undated (Box 43)
    - Purchasing Clerk, undated (Box 43)
    - Receptionist, undated (Box 43)
    - Recruiter, undated (Box 43)
    - Related Instructor, undated (Box 43)
    - Reproduction Clerk, undated (Box 43)
    - Research Assistant, undated (Box 43)
    - Research Aide, 1966 (Box 43)
    - Research Aide Program, 1967 (Box 43)
    - Reference Data, undated (Box 43)
    - Research Director, undated (Box 43)
    - Research Technician, undated (Box 43)
    - Secretary, undated (Box 43)
    - Secretary - Receptionist, undated (Box 43)
    - Secretary and Job Corps Intake Clerk, undated (Box 43)
    - Secretarial Supervisor, undated (Box 43)
    - Senior Foreman, undated (Box 43)
    - Senior Secretary, undated (Box 43)
    - Senior Secretary - Education, undated (Box 43)
    - Senior Secretary - Field Operations, undated (Box 43)
    - Senior Secretary - Financial Officer, undated (Box 43)
    - Staffing patterns and job description, undated; 2 folders (Box 43)
    - Study Center Supervisor, undated (Box 43)
    - Study Center or Teacher Aides, undated (Box 43)
    - Switchboard Operator, undated (Box 43)
    - Teacher Aide, undated (Box 43)
    - Unit Administration, undated (Box 43)
    - Various job descriptions, undated (Box 44)
    - Work Shop Specialist, undated (Box 44)
    - Youth Work Specialist, undated (Box 44)
  - Office files
    - Accident reports, 1965-1966 (Box 44)
    - Administration memos, 1966 (Box 44)
    - Administration minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 44)
    - Administrative guidelines, 1966 (Box 44)
    - Administrative procedures memos, 1964 (Box 44)
    - All staff memos and information, 1967 (Box 44)
    - Application for employment, blank, undated (Box 44)
    - Bank directors, undated (Box 44)
    - Biographical sketch, Ernest Boston, 1967 (Box 44)
    - Blank forms, 1965 (Box 44)
    - Board of Directors, 1966 (Box 44)
    - Brochures, 1964-1965 (Box 44)
    - Bus confirmations, 1966 (Box 44)
    - Business operators, 1966 (Box 44)
    - By-law changes, 1966 (Box 44)
    - Car registrations, 1966-1967; 3 folders (Box 44)
    - CFO local travel expense sheets, 1966 (Box 44)
    - Change on personnel records forms, undated (Box 45)
    - Commission, 1966 (Box 45)
    - Congressional committees, 1966 (Box 45)
    - Consumable supplies, 1967 (Box 45)
    - County election results, 1965 (Box 45)
    - Day file, October 1966-February 1967; 6 folders (Box 45)
    - Day file, Charles Crowley, 1966 (Box 45)
    - Day file, memos, Feb 1967 (Box 45)
    - Day file, secretarial hints, 1966 (Box 45)
    - Day file, writing style guide, 1966 (Box 45)
    - Day files for the week, 1967; 11 folders (Box 45)
    - Demonstration cities, HUD, 1966 (Box 45)
    - Directors meeting, 1967 (Box 45)
    - Directory of staff members, 1965 (Box 45)
    - Draft contract, standard OEO form, 1966 (Box 45)
    - Education programs fact sheet, 1965 (Box 46)
    - Employee ID cards, 1966 (Box 46)
    - Employee vehicle use forms, undated (Box 46)
    - Federal employment, 1966 (Box 46)
    - Gerber's day file, October 1966-February 1967 (Box 46)
    - Group Health Insurance, 1967 (Box 46)
    - Identification cards, 1966 (Box 46)
    - Information on new payroll system, undated (Box 46)
    - Job applications, blank, undated (Box 46)
    - Key access list, 1965 (Box 46)
    - Labels, undated (Box 46)
    - Labels for board of directors, undated (Box 46)
    - Leases, 1967 (Box 46)
    - Log of forms, 1966 (Box 46)
    - Mailing lists, 1966 (Box 46)
    - Medical care - employment, 1965-1967 (Box 46)
    - Medicare information, 1966 (Box 46)
    - Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 46)
    - Miscellaneous lists and forms, 1967 (Box 46)
    - Monthly reports, 1967 (Box 46)
    - Neighborhood board chairman and Norman Hill, labels, undated (Box 46)
    - Notice of meetings, 1967 (Box 46)
    - Office furniture, 1965 (Box 46)
    - Office memos, 1965-1966 (Box 46)
    - Office of Education Programs that can Benefit the Disadvantaged and the Handicapped, 1966 (Box 46)
    - Office equipment inventory, undated (Box 374)
    - Office space, 1966 (Box 46)
    - OMAT - OJT contract #82-31-40, blank 18 month budget, blank forms, 1966 (Box 46)
    - OMAT - OJT contract #82-31-40, blank budget report, 1966 (Box 46)
    - OMAT - OJT contract #82-31-40, blank invoice forms, 1966 (Box 46)
    - Onondaga County Maps, NYS maps, Circa 1964 (Box 46)
    - Organizational chart, 1966 (Oversize 1)
    - Organizational interference, 1966 (Box 47)
    - Orientation schedule, 1965 (Box 47)
    - Orientation sessions, 1966 (Box 47)
    - Payroll and time card information, 1966 (Box 47)
    - Personnel policy, 1965 (Box 47)
    - Persons suspended from Crusade for Opportunity, undated (Box 47)
    - Policy directive 1-66, Internal revenue withholdings on enrollee wages, 1966 (Box 47)
    - Policy directive 3-65, duration of enrollment, hours of week, wages, and fringe benefits for enrollees, 1966 (Box 47)
    - Program description, 1966 (Box 47)
    - Proposed staff structure, 1967 (Box 47)
    - Reference forms, 1965 (Box 47)
    - Request for reproduction supplies, blank, 1967 (Box 47)
    - Research Aide rejection and offer letters, 1967 (Box 47)
    - Rita McVey files, Office Manager
      - Administration, 1966 (Box 356)
      - Credit union, 1965-1966 (Box 47)
      - Education division, personnel folder, 1965-1966 (Box 47)
      - Employment division, general, 1966 (Box 47)
      - Neighborhood Youth Corps, personnel folder, 1966 (Box 47)
      - Research (1-18) evaluation, personnel, 1966 (Box 47)
      - Teachers/Teachers Aides, personnel, 1965-1966 (Box 47)
      - Verification of earnings, personnel, 1965 (Box 47)
    - Schedule of meetings, 1966-1967 (Box 47)
    - Schedule of weekly meetings, 1966-1967; 3 folders (Box 47)
    - Senior staff, 1967 (Box 47)
    - Senior staff telephone directory, undated (Box 47)
    - Social Security amendments, 1965 (Box 47)
    - Staff roster, 1966; 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Staffing patterns and job description, 1966-1967 (Box 47)
    - Terms and conditions governing contracts between Community Action Program agency and contract for conduct, 1966 (Box 48)
    - Time cards, undated (Box 48)
    - Time reports, blank, undated (Box 48)
    - Title V, 1965 (Box 48)
    - Travel vouchers, 1966 (Box 48)
    - Volunteer cards, 1966 (Box 48)
    - Weekly Events (centers), 1965-1966 (Box 48)
    - Weekly meetings, 1967 (Box 48)
    - Weekly schedule of meetings, 1967 (Box 48)
    - Work papers, 1966 (Box 48)
    - Writing paper, blank, undated (Box 48)
    - Xerox corporation, 1967 (Box 48)
    - Xerox general file, 1965 (Box 48)
    - Zipcode numbers, undated (Box 48)
  - Personnel
    - Administration memos to personnel, 1967 (Box 48)
    - Agency placement services, 1967 (Box 48)
    - Applications
      - Administrative positions, 1965-1966 (Box 48)
      - Business and Purchasing, 1967 (Box 48)
      - Clerical, 1967 (Box 48)
      - Community services, 1967 (Box 48)
      - Counselor, 1967 (Box 48)
      - East Side, 1967 (Box 48)
      - Education Specialist, 1967 (Box 48)
      - Far East Side, 1967 (Box 48)
      - Full-time Head Start day care, 1967 (Box 48)
      - Legal Services, 1966 (Box 48)
      - letter A, 1966; 2 folders (Box 48)
      - letter B, 1966; 4 folders (Box 49)
      - letter C, 1966; 4 folders (Box 49)
      - letter D, 1964-1966; 4 folders (Box 50)
      - letter E, 1964-1966; 3 folders (Box 50)
      - letter F, 1964-1966; 4 folders (Box 50)
      - letter G, 1964-1966 (Box 50)
      - letter G, 1964-1966; 3 folders (Box 51)
      - letter H, 1966; 4 folders (Box 51)
      - letter I, 1965 (Box 52)
      - letter J, 1964-1966; 2 folders (Box 52)
      - letter K, 1964-1966; 2 folders (Box 52)
      - letter L, 1964-1966; 3 folders (Box 52)
      - letter M, 1966 (Box 52)
      - letter N, 1966 (Box 52)
      - letter O, 1966 (Box 52)
      - letter P, 1966 (Box 52)
      - letter R, 1966 (Box 52)
      - letter S, 1966; 2 folders (Box 53)
      - letter T, 1966 (Box 53)
      - letter V, 1966 (Box 53)
      - letter W, 1966 (Box 53)
      - Miscellaneous, 1967; 2 folders (Box 53)
      - Open - grammar school, 1967 (Box 53)
      - Open - high school, 1967 (Box 53)
      - Personnel Officer or Assistant, 1967 (Box 53)
      - Research department, 1967 (Box 53)
      - Secretarial, 1967 (Box 53)
      - Some college, 1967 (Box 53)
      - Tallman, 1967; 2 folders (Box 53)
      - Teacher, Youth Worker, 1967 (Box 53)
      - West and North Side, 1967 (Box 53)
    - Appointment letters, 1967; 2 folders (Box 54)
    - Charles Crawley files
      - East Side Center, personnel schedule, 1966 (Box 54)
      - Employee evaluations, personnel, 1966 (Box 54)
      - Employment opportunities, 1966 (Box 54)
      - Far East Side Center personnel file, 1966 (Box 54)
      - Home Aides application, 1966 (Box 54)
      - House/education committee, 1966 (Box 54)
      - Housing program, staff, personnel, 1966 (Box 54)
      - In-service training clerical, 1966 (Box 54)
      - Jack Anderson program, probationary period, 1966 (Box 54)
      - Legal program, correspondence, 1966 (Box 54)
      - Miscellaneous, 1965-1966 (Box 54)
      - Miscellaneous data, 1966 (Box 54)
      - Morning report, 1966 (Box 54)
      - Professional placement correspondence, 1966 (Box 54)
      - Tallman Center, 1966 (Box 54)
      - William Streets, data, 1966-1967 (Box 54)
    - Credit union material, 1966 (Box 54)
    - Employment applications, 1966 (Box 54)
    - Employment department personnel, 1966-1967 (Box 54)
    - Equitable Life Assurance Company of NY, 1966 (Box 54)
    - Evaluations, 1966 (Box 54)
    - Financial Director appointment, 1967 (Box 54)
    - Group hospital insurance, correspondence, 1963-1969 (Box 54)
    - Group life and hospital insurance, notice of coverage, 1965 (Box 54)
    - Health insurance, hospital form, blank, undated (Box 54)
    - Health insurance, physicians form, blank, undated (Box 54)
    - Inactive file, 1966 (Box 54)
    - Insurance conversion to individual health, undated (Box 54)
    - Insurance group hospital statement of health, undated (Box 54)
    - Insurance group life death claims, undated (Box 54)
    - Insurance policies, 1963-1964 (Box 54)
    - Insurance proposals (with employee census), 1965 (Box 55)
    - Job applications, blank, 1966 (Box 55)
    - Late application memos, 1966 (Box 55)
    - Late personnel transactions, 1966 (Box 55)
    - Life and health insurance, schedule for employee reinstatement, blank, undated (Box 55)
    - Life insurance, change of beneficiary, undated (Box 55)
    - Open - College grads, 1967 (Box 55)
    - Open - group work, 1967 (Box 55)
    - Personnel applications, 1964-1967; 2 folders (Box 55)
    - Personnel changes, 1965-1967 (Box 55)
    - Personnel changes for payroll, 1965; 3 folders (Box 55)
    - Personnel department memos, 1966-1967 (Box 55)
    - Personnel directory, 1966 (Box 55)
    - Personnel file, Legal Services, 1967 (Box 55)
    - Personnel file, Office of Economic Opportunity, correspondence, 1967 (Box 55)
    - Personnel form edit review, 1967 (Box 55)
    - Personnel handbook, first draft, undated (Box 55)
    - Personnel memos, 1966 (Box 55)
    - Personnel policies manual, 1966 (Box 168)
    - Personnel policies manual, table of contents, undated; 2 folders (Box 168)
    - Personnel records
      - letter D, 1965-1967; 27 folders (Box 56)
        Personnel records restricted until 2067.
      - letter E, 1965-1967; 5 folders (Box 56)
      - letter E, 1965-1967; 4 folders (Box 57)
      - letter F, 1965-1967; 28 folders (Box 57)
      - letter G, 1965-1967; 19 folders (Box 57)
      - letter G, 1965-1967; 33 folders (Box 58)
      - letter H, 1964-1967; 6 folders (Box 58)
      - letter H, 1964-1967; 41 folders (Box 59)
      - letter H, 1964-1967; 7 folders (Box 60)
      - letter I, 1966-1967; 5 folders (Box 60)
      - letter J, 1964-1967; 29 folders (Box 60)
      - letter J, 1965-1967; 3 folders (Box 61)
      - letter K, 1965-1967; 2 folders (Box 61)
      - letter M, 1965-1967; 16 folders (Box 61)
      - letter N, 1967; 2 folders (Box 61)
      - letter O, 1965-1967; 19 folders (Box 61)
      - letter P, 1964-1967; 44 folders (Box 62)
      - letter P, 1965-1967; 3 folders (Box 63)
      - letter R, 1964-1967; 39 folders (Box 63)
      - letter R, 1966-1967; 4 folders (Box 64)
      - letter S, 1964-1967; 48 folders (Box 64)
      - letter S, 1965-1967; 24 folders (Box 65)
      - letter T, 1964-1967; 10 folders (Box 65)
      - letter T, 1964-1967; 12 folders (Box 66)
      - letter V, 1964-1967; 6 folders (Box 66)
      - letter W, 1964-1967; 17 folders (Box 66)
      - letter W, 1964-1967; 29 folders (Box 67)
      - letter Z, 1962-1966; 3 folders (Box 67)
    - Personnel roster, 1966 (Box 68)
    - Personnel transaction, 1966 (Box 68)
    - Program development memos to personnel, 1967 (Box 68)
    - Resignation letters, 1966-1967 (Box 68)
    - Research memos to Personnel department, 1967 (Box 68)
    - Reproduction Clerk, employment applications, 1966 (Box 68)
    - Request for supplies, newspaper advertisements, 1966-1967 (Box 68)
    - Ruth Gamm application, 1966 (Box 68)
    - Secretary memo, time cards, etc., 1965-1967 (Box 68)
    - Senior staff evaluations, undated (Box 356)
    - Staff roster, October-December 1965 (Box 68)
    - Staff roster (updated), 1966-1967 (Box 68)
    - Summer program, terminations, miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 68)
    - Social work applications, 1967 (Box 68)
    - Staff recruitment, 1966 (Box 68)
    - Terminations and hiring letters, 1965-1966 (Box 68)
    - Time sheets, undated (Box 68)
    - US Department of Labor, correspondence with personnel department, 1967 (Box 68)
    - Workmen's compensation, 1966 (Box 68)
    - Workmen's compensation, C-2 forms, undated (Box 68)
    - Workmen's compensation, C11 forms, undated (Box 68)
  - Reports
    - Analysis of the CFO, undated; 2 folders (Box 68)
    - Annual report, 1965; 2 folders (Box 68)
    - Annual report, 1966-1967 (Box 69)
    - Annual report for fiscal year 1966 with a "capsule" view of the six months ended December 31, 1966 (Box 69)
    - Community Action Program status report, 1967 (Box 69)
    - Monthly report - outline, 1965-1966; 3 folders (Box 69)
    - Monthly report, Nov 1965-Jan 1966; 6 folders (Box 69)
    - Monthly report, Jan 1966-Jun 1966; 10 folders (Box 70)
    - Monthly report, Jul 1966-May 1967; 11 folders (Box 71)
    - Monthly reports, miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 71)
    - Monthly reports, narratives, 1967 (Box 71)
    - OEO report, 1966 (Box 71)
    - OEO monthly report, 1966 (Box 361)
    - OMAT bimonthly report, Dec 1964-Feb 1965 (Box 71)
    - OMAT bimonthly report, Jul 1966-Apr 1967; 12 folders (Box 72)
    - OMAT reports, drafts, 1965-1966 (Box 73)
    - OMAT reports, monthly, 1965 (Box 73)
    - OMAT reports, statistical data, 1967 (Box 73)
    - Program progress reports, 1967 (Box 73)
    - Program reports, Oct 1964-Jul 1965; 7 folders (Box 73)
    - Program reports, Jul-Oct 1965; 2 folders (Box 74)
    - Program reports, community services, Nov 1964-Jul 1965; 6 folders (Box 74)
    - Program reports, education, Jan 1965-Feb 1967; 5 folders (Box 74)
    - Program reports, legal services, May-June 1965 (Box 74)
    - Program reports, youth workers and recreation, Jun 1965 (Box 75)
    - Program reports, youth worker project, Jul 1965 (Box 75)
    - Program directors reports, 1965 (Box 75)
    - Program's Achivements: An Excerpt from the Annual Report to the Membership, Oct 1965
    - Quarterly report, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 75)
    - Quarterly report to OEO, Jan-Mar 1966 (Box 75)
    - Reports from agencies to Chest on Council, regarding Action Area Recreation, 1965
    - Slide presentation, discussion draft, 1965 (Box 75)
    - The State of the Agency, Feb 1967 (Box 75)
  - Senior staff files
    - Acousta, John files, See Research files: Staff files: Acousta, John files
    - Anderson, Jack (John) files, Deputy of Programs
      - 6 month projection, 1966-1967 (Box 75)
      - 6 months, 1967 budget, 2 folders (Box 75)
      - Ad hoc personnel, 1965 (Box 75)
      - Administration, 1967; 3 folders (Box 75)
      - Administration bulletins, 1964-1965 (Box 75)
      - Administration, personnel, 1966-1967 (Box 75)
      - Administrative assistants, 1967 (Box 75)
      - Advocacy in the Ghetto, Richard Cloward, Richard Elman, 1966 (Box 75)
      - Aged, 1965-1967; 2 folders (Box 75)
      - Agency training, 1964-1965 (Box 76)
      - All day staff meeting, 1965 (Box 76)
      - American Institute of Religion, 1966 (Box 76)
      - Annual meeting, 1967 (Box 76)
      - Applications (personnel), 1966; 2 folders (Box 76)
      - Basic Data Pertaining to Neighborhood Board Areas, George Hall, 1966 (Box 76)
      - Ben Zimmerman, 1965; 2 folders (Box 76)
      - Bessie C. Manuel, 1966-1967 (Box 76)
      - Board minutes, 1965 (Box 76)
      - Board of Directors, 1965; 3 folders (Box 76)
      - Budget report, 1965; 2 folders (Box 76)
      - Budget review, undated (Box 76)
      - Bureau of Work programs, budget, 1967 (Box 76)
      - Business office, 1966-1967 (Box 76)
      - By-laws, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 76)
      - C.A.M.P (Cooperative Area Manpower Planning), 1967 (Box 76)
      - Campership program, summer, 1966 (Box 76)
      - Camping information, 1967 (Box 76)
      - Career information service/Peace Corp applications, 1966 (Box 76)
      - CFO and welfare, contract (Box 77)
      - Community Action Program forms, blank, 1966 (Box 77)
      - Community Action Program memos, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 77)
      - CAP statistical report, 1966 (Box 77)
      - Community Chest, 1966 (Box 77)
      - Community services, 1966; 5 folders (Box 77)
      - Community services panel, 1965 (Box 77)
      - Community services, legal service, Jul 1965 (Box 77)
      - Computer Center, Syracuse University, 1965 (Box 77)
      - Condition committee, 1967 (Box 77)
      - Conference reports: William Burton, 1967 (Box 77)
      - Consultants, 1963-1965 (Box 77)
      - Correspondence, 1964-1967; 6 folders (Box 78)
      - Correspondence and memos with business office, 1966-1967 (Box 78)
      - Correspondence and memos with program coordinators, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 78)
      - Correspondence and memos with program staff, 1966-1967 (Box 78)
      - Correspondence control (old), 1966 (Box 78)
      - Correspondence with James Tillman, 1966-1967; 3 folders (Box 78)
      - Correspondence with Leslie Garodnick, May 1967 (Box 78)
      - Correspondence, incoming, 1966-1967 (Box 78)
      - Correspondence, outgoing, 1966-1967 (Box 78)
      - County development, 1965 (Box 79)
      - County Penn Program, 1965 (Box 79)
      - Curriculum Development committee, 1967 (Box 79)
      - Curriculum Materials Development Center, 1966-1967 (Box 79)
      - Day care, 1966-1967; 7 folders (Box 79)
      - Day Care task force, 1966-1967 (Box 80)
      - Defense fund, 1967 (Box 80)
      - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, correspondence, 1967 (Box 80)
      - Deputy for Programs, 1967 (Box 80)
      - East Side Education committee, 1967 (Box 80)
      - Education, 1965-1967; 6 folders (Box 80)
      - Education center, 1965 (Box 80)
      - Education committee (joint), 1966-1967 (Box 80)
      - Education coordinators, 1967 (Box 80)
      - Educational Aide training, 1966 (Box 80)
      - Employee committee (joint), 1967 (Box 80)
      - Employment, 1965; 3 folders (Box 80)
      - Employment, 1966-1967; 10 folders (Box 81)
      - Employment recreation, 1967 (Box 82)
      - Employment staff training, 1967 (Box 82)
      - Employment statistical reports, 1966 (Box 82)
      - Establishing In-service training, 1964-1966
      - Executive staff meetings, 1965 (Box 82)
      - Extra copies of reproduced materials, 1966-1967 (Box 82)
      - Field operations, 1966-1967 (Box 82)
      - Field operations memos, 1966 (Box 82)
      - Field operations minutes, 1965 (Box 82)
      - Field operations personnel, 1966-1967 (Box 82)
      - Films 8mm proposal, 1965 (Box 82)
      - Finance committee (joint budget advisory committee), 1966-1967 (Box 82)
      - Freund case, 1967 (Box 82)
      - General, 1965-1965 (Box 82)
      - General information and letter from Newton Allen regarding Title I, 1966 (Box 82)
      - General staff meetings, 1967 (Box 82)
      - Head Start, 1966-1967; 5 folders (Box 82)
      - Head Start, 1967; 2 folders (Box 83)
      - Head Start application, 1967 (Box 83)
      - Head Start personnel, 1967 (Box 83)
      - Health, 1966-1967 (Box 83)
      - Hollis West resignation, 1967 (Box 83)
      - Home Aides, Inc., 1966-1967; 3 folders (Box 83)
      - Home Town News, 1967 (Box 83)
      - Housing, 1966 (Box 83)
      - Human Rights Commission of Syracuse and Onondaga County, 1966 (Box 83)
      - Indian reservation, 1966-1967 (Box 83)
      - Indian reservation, personnel, 1966-1967 (Box 83)
      - Information and referral memos, 1966 (Box 83)
      - Inner city recreation, 1966 (Box 83)
      - In-service training, 1964-1966; 4 folders (Box 83)
      - In-service training, 1966; 2 folders (Box 84)
      - In-service training, personnel, 1966-1967 (Box 84)
      - James Tillman miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 84)
      - Job Corps, 1967 (Box 84)
      - Job descriptions, 1966; 2 folders (Box 84)
      - Joint Neighborhood Planning committee, 1967 (Box 84)